Guide to the Stanford University, School of Engineering, Requisitions
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, School of Engineering, requisitions
1926-1946
SC0171B
Stanford University. School of Engineering.
4 Linear feet
Requisitions from the Dept. of Civil Engineering, 1926-40, the Dept. of Electrical Engineering, 1926-40, Ryan High Voltage Laboratory, 1930-40, Dept. of Mechanical Engineering, 1926-46, Guggenheim Aeronautic Laboratory, 1927-44, and the Dept. of Mining Engineering, 1936-40. Also includes one folder on the Klystron micro-wave measurement account, 1939-40.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, 1977.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Requisitions from the Dept. of Civil Engineering, 1926-40, the Dept. of Electrical Engineering, 1926-40, Ryan High Voltage Laboratory, 1930-40, Dept. of Mechanical Engineering, 1926-46, Guggenheim Aeronautic Laboratory, 1927-44, and the Dept. of Mining Engineering, 1936-40. Also includes one folder on the Klystron micro-wave measurement account, 1939-40.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Guggenheim Aeronautic Laboratory.; Stanford University. Ryan High Voltage Laboratory.; Stanford University. School of Engineering.; Engineering--Supplies.; Klystrons.; Requisitions.
Collection Contents
- Requisiitonss
  - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1926-1940
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Civil Engineering Department Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1926-1940
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1936?-1937 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Electrical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Electrical Engineering Illumination Lab Safeway Fund, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Electrical Engineering ISEC Research, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Electrical Engineering IT and T, 1934-1940 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Electrical Engineering IT and T, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Klystron Micro-Wave Measurement Account, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1930-1940
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Electrical Engineering Ryan Laboratory Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1926-1945
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1940 Sep 3-1941 Aug 23 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1940 Sep 5-1941 Aug 28 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1941 Aug 30-1942 Sep 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1941 Sep 10-1942 Sep 17 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1942 Sep 4-1944 Aug 23 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1942 Sep 9-1944 Aug 24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1944 Sep 15-1945 Aug 27 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1944-1946
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1944 Oct 4-1945 Aug 20 (Box 2a, Folder 23)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department Requisitions, 1945 Sep 1-1946 Sep 21 (Box 2a, Folder 24)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1927-1942
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Air Propeller Research (discontinued September 1, 1928), circa 1928 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1940 Sep 3-1941 Aug 27 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1940 Sep 5-1941 Aug 28 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1941 Aug 30-1942 Sep 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1941-1944
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1941 Sep 9-1942 Sep 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1942 Sep 4-1944 Sep 25 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Requisitions, 1942 Sep 4-1944 Sep 25 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mining Engineering Requisitions, 1936-1940
    - Mining Engineering Requisitions, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Mining Engineering Requisitions, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mining Engineering Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Mining Engineering Requisitions, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)